-How could you add weight to the global font definition to win over the classes added by point 3?
You could use something similar to this:
* { 						 
    font-family: fantasy;
}
-Imagine there is a declaration like class=”oh-no-inline-styles” style=”background:red” and you need to change the background to green without changing the inline style. How could you accomplish this?
You can use "important!" because online styles override css styles.